Ladies and gentlemen, I have a two of those invocation by the pastor at First Assembly. God Mr. Raymond for selling to me he's retiring in office so we may not see him very much more time-
Very many more times!
Let us pray together heavily. Fatherly thank you all who give your son Jesus We pray Your continued blessing on my amover home up All our transitions Pray from our first responders For protection upon them Our churches
And businesses at your hand and step on them in blessed Him. All we thank you for our continued protection For the health, or with this COVID-19 to Thank You Lord
Just covering us & letting life come like that To put Your blessings That continue
We just ask those Jesus precious thing Amen
I'll see you all later in the development of 430 North Maine. Christian Harry
What the building currently looks like today This is going to be a Him processing facility, just to remind you of what's Going To In Here in front
And this is Bait for Maven. Actually it was freshly but they also do business with them all Of their current locations are gonna stay
But they already have here in town. They anticipate hiring up to 15 full-time employees at a wage of 14,000 and $15 an hour
It's A nonconvestible process using CO2 To Process the Him
They'll do about a $1.5 million renovation on the current building
There's tenants that are missing portion of it building they're gonna remain
That part and this is just to remind you, art used To be The Audit Leadership if You Can Remember Back in
They expect to be operational by September and this is rendering of what they believe the outside will look like
I know that when we're here at The Meeting, last time it did say That It Would Be Re-doing
And Christian basically we're being asked to wave in Spection Fee's and a few other things
They already have utilities, they are all that is going To be the little left of the Robloft subtyping keys for when
They go in and demo the inside of it, an any inspection. Yeah
So stuff to get permits inspections but those type things
But that's why its coming before then MSMA is because Of The Solid Waste aspect
We got a few labor was also included clawback claws
If they don't fulfill certain parts this agreement
That we're making them their livelihood for re-enversing and seeing For Those Costs
You need questions for Christy
Tom and I just asked Chris he did presenting in because we do have a new chairman come to you
And so be aware of everything
Well that building has been sitting vacant. For i guess it was the second hand store resale shop
Wow, well
We have a lot of time
And we had to go around the new sensations and broken windows
All brass, it's going To be a real blessing
I think that has, yeah, we've been especially right there on this six weeks
So how about working nice together
Okay are you asking for any action
Is This where?
We talked about it before the year of resolution
Okay, do we have most to approve The Resolution?
Approving community financial support and fee waivers for Fresh Leaf LLC
So in a second I'll second that roll call please
Hi
All right, Louis Western
Thank you. Christy
Any new business anyone
Staff reports or any packet
Any staff available for any questions
You need trustee community announcements
I'm 13 is a gentleman. Do we have all the dreams?
Yes, you are meeting some of it and second
We'll call please